Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Labor-Management Pension Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 244, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statement by Harvey W. Brown - What's ahead in human relations in industry?, 1947; Publication (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Address by H.W. Brown - What labor expects of management, 1948; Publication (Box 244, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Cayuga Lodge No. 1607, Publication (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Notice - Election - December 9, 1959, Publication (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Supreme Court of the United States, Oct. Term, 1918, no. 556: Duplex Printing Press Company, Appellant, vs. Emil J. Deering and William BramleyMotion to advance, Publication (Box 244, Folder 6)
    Author: Emil J. Deering; William Bramley
  - Item 3: Supreme Court of Georgia, April Term, 1959 - 20,428. International Assoc. of Machinists, et al., v. S.B. Street, Nancy M. Looper, et al. decided May 8, 1959., Publication (Box 244, Folder 6)
    Author: Nancy M. Looper
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Roster of Grand Lodge, District, and Local Lodge Officers.Oct. 15, 1949, Publication (Box 244, Folder 7)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Teaching outline for Steward's training, 1957; Publication (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Program, Conference on The Role of Labor in the International Scene, 1952; Publication (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Experiment in St. Louis around the world in two days, 1952; Publication (Box 244, Folder 8)
    Notes: reprinted from Machinists Monthly Journal, July, 1952. 2 copies
  - Item 4: Machinist Apprenticeship Standards jointly adopted by Representative employers and the International Association of Machinists.St. Louis, Missouri and Vicinity, 1941; Publication (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Manual for Stewards and Committeemen, 1944; Publication (Box 244, Folder 8)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, District No. 9, I.A. of M. Welfare Association Trust, 1954; Publication (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Manual for Stewards and Committeemen, 1949; Publication (Box 244, Folder 9)
    Notes: Preliminary Draft, Tentative & Confidential
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 65th Anniversary of District Lodge 15 and building dedication, 1958; Publication (Box 244, Folder 10)
- Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge No. 727, Publication (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Union Chairman's Manual, 1942; Publication (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Union Chairman's Manual, 1944; Publication (Box 244, Folder 11)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: For Immediate Release - Lodge 616 IAM/AW wins bargaining rights., 1966; Publication (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: District 157 Self Portrait conducted by Senior Public Relations Class, Utica College, Utica, New York, 1961; Publication (Box 244, Folder 12)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Education Dept., Publication (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: IAM handbook for Lodge Education Committees, 1966; Publication (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Guide for instructing Local Lodge Officers, 1966; Publication (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Effective communication, 1967; Publication (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The truth about the Taft-Hartley Law and its consequences to the labor movement, Publication (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Teaching outline for Steward's training (draft), 1957; Publication (Box 245, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Education Dept., Publication (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: IAM Teaching Outline for Stewards' duties and Grievance handling, 1966; Publication (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: IAM Education Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.69-2, 69-3, 70-1
  - Item 3: IAM Special bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.1,9,11,15
  - Item 4: This is brief outline of basic facts on the structure, government and activities of the IAM', 1957; Publication (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: List of IAM Educational Mat'l., 1957; Publication (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: IAM Education Dept. Discussion outline, 1950; Publication (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Misc. flyers, Publication (Box 245, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Education Dept., Publication (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Grievance Procedure (adopted from the Teaching Outline for Stewards' Training), 1957; Publication (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Shop steward training outline and discussion guide for six separate two-hour training sessions, 1952; Publication (Box 245, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Education Dept., Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: IAM Bulletin, 1957; Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.2, 5-6, 8, 10 (1957)
  - Item 2: IAM Bulletin, 1958; Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.2,4-6 (1958)
  - Item 3: IAM Bulletin, 1959; Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.1-3 (1959)
  - Item 4: IAM Bulletin, 1960; Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.4 (1960)
  - Item 5: IAM Bulletin, Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
    Notes: Special Bulletin no.1-6, 8, 10
  - Item 6: IAM Education Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 245, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Education Dept., Publication (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: IAM Bulletin, 1959; Publication (Box 245, Folder 5)
    Notes: no. 4, 6-8 (1959)
  - Item 2: IAM Bulletin, 1960; Publication (Box 245, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1-6 (1960)
  - Item 3: IAM Bulletin, 1961; Publication (Box 245, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1-4 (1961)
  - Item 4: IAM Bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 245, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1-5 (1962)
  - Item 5: IAM Bulletin, 1963; Publication (Box 245, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1 (1963)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM). Education Dept., Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: IAM Bulletin, 1963; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 2-3 (1963)
  - Item 2: IAM Bulletin, 1964; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-2, 4 (1964)
  - Item 3: IAM Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-4 (1966)
  - Item 4: IAM Bulletin, 1967; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-5 (1967)
  - Item 5: IAM Bulletin, 1968; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-5 (1968)
  - Item 6: IAM Bulletin, 1969; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-3 (1969)
  - Item 7: IAM Bulletin, 1970; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1, 3-5 (1970)
  - Item 8: IAM Bulletin, 1971; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-3 (1971)
  - Item 9: IAM Bulletin, 1972; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1, 3 (1972)
  - Item 10: IAM Bulletin, 1973; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-2 (1973)
  - Item 11: IAM Bulletin, 1974; Publication (Box 245, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.1-2 (1974)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Officers' guide to aid local lodge officers in the performance of their duties, 1963; Publication (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Teaching outline for Stewards' training, Publication (Box 245, Folder 7)
    Notes: final
  - Item 3: 1962 IAM Machinists Leadership Schools, Publication (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Misc. flyers, Publication (Box 245, Folder 7)
    Notes: flyers
  - Item 5: a handbook for Local Lodge Education Committees, 1962; Publication (Box 245, Folder 7)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Shop Committee Card; World War II Fact Sheet; Correspondence; Shop Steward's manual; New York State Unemployment Insurance; Insurance for workers and their families; Digest of New York State Disability Benefits Laws; New York State Regulations unde, Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
    Notes: Misc. flyers and info sheets gathered in a kind of booklet
  - Item 2: Labors' stake in the public school, Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Toward a better, stronger America, Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: What does labor want?, Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Labor and the elections, Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Profile of International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The Machinist - Special Section, 1962; Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
    Notes: newspaper
  - Item 8: Remarks made by A.J. Hayes, at the Industrial Managemen Club, 1960; Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: A Handbook for organizers, 1950; Publication (Box 245, Folder 8)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Machinists Monthly Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Your union today, 1963; Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Half a century with the International Association of Machinists - A brief sketch marking high lights and mileposts in fifty years of progress and achievement, 1938; Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: What is Trade Unionism?, Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
    Author: Educational Committee of the Ladies' Auxiliary to the IAM
    Notes: no.3
  - Item 5: The Worker and his wife and the public schools, Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.8
  - Item 6: The Necessity for higher education, Publication (Box 245, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.9
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Machinist - Special Section, 1959; Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Statement, before the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1947; Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The truth about the Taft-Hartley Law and its consequences to the labor movement, Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Statement, before the House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1949; Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Statement, before the Senate Subcommittee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1949; Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Men and monopolies, Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Historical Record, Machinists-Carpenters dispute (issued May 29, 1941, by Authority of AF of L Executive Council), Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Handbook on the National Labor Relations Act and N.L.R.B. procedure, Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: A guide for IAM legislative committees, 1970; Publication (Box 246, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: History of Greater New York Lodge Local 68, 1921; Publication (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of General Executive Board, Year 1921, Publication (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: In the matter of 1948 wage negotiations between unions and companies signatory to the Pacific Coast master shipbuilding and repair agreements: supporting brief of the Pacific Coast District Metal Trades Council, Publication (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: In the matter of arbitration proceedings between Machinists' Union, Local 79, International Association of Machinists and Washington Metal Trades, Inc.: Union opening brief, 1946; Publication (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Machinists Strike, Open letter from machinists lodge no. 68, Publication (Box 246, Folder 2)
    Notes: flyer. 2 copies
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Local ---- Welcomes you, your shop steward is, 1965; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
    Notes: welcome flyer
  - Item 2: 1670 News (1/25/60), 1960; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1962; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Correspondence, 1962; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Correspondence, 1965; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: A-M News, Home Office Edition (Sept. 1961), Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Machinists: 75 years old, by Railroaders in Atlanta, Ga., 1963; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: 1607 News - vol. III-VI, Special Issue, One year anniv ed, 1968-1974 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Machinist News - State Conference Issue, 1953; Publication (Box 246, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Ithaca Machinist, 1953; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Shop stewards' manual, Aeronautical Mechanics Lodge 756, 1944; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Local Lodge, 1955; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1 (Dec. 1955)
  - Item 4: Minutes, 1949; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Forward or Backward, 1957; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Correspondence, 1958; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: ? - published monthly, 1955; Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Machinists Monthly Journal, Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Misc. flyers, Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Pension plan: Chase Brass & Copper Co., Incorporated, UAW-CIO, Local 1108, Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Social progress and trade unions in the United States, Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Machinist News - vol.3, no.2-6 (1954); vol.2, no.1-4, 6-11 (1953); vol.2, no.6-9 (1952), 1952-1954 (Box 246, Folder 5)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Legislative Report (1958-1959) (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Your union, Production and Aeronautical Lodge 1327, International Association of Machinists, AF of L, Publication (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Executive Session of the Fifteenth Convention of the International Association of Machinists, Baltimore, MD., Thursday, June 29, 1916, to Monday, July 3, 1916., Publication (Box 246, Folder 6)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Public Relations Report (1958-1959) (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Education report (Sept. 1958), Rochester, New York, Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Conference call (Dec. 31, 1958), Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: New York State Council 26th Semi-Annual Conference, 1957; Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Packet from 29th Semi-Annual Conference (Feb 28-Mar 1, 1959), Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: This is FDR, 1944; Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Leadership training program for stewards, shop committeemen and lodge officers in six sessions, 1945; Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert Schrank
  - Item 8: You and your Governor Averell Harriman, a guide to Victory in 1958, Publication (Box 246, Folder 7)
    Notes: campaign booklet
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Leadership training program for stewards, shop committeemen and lodge officers in six sessions, 1945; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1944; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: 12th Semi-Annual Meeting.minutes, 1950; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Packet from 28th Semi-Annual Conference, 1958; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
    Notes: Sept. 13-14, 1958
  - Item 5: Legislative Report, 1958; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Legislative Report, 1956; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
    Notes: Feb. 25-26, 1956
  - Item 7: Public Relations, 1956; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
    Notes: Feb. 25, 1956
  - Item 8: Minutes of the 23rd Semi-Annual Conference, 1956; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Report on Starting Lodge Publications, with recommendations and suggestions, 1957; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Address by General Vice-President Fred Coonley, Int'l. Assoc. of Machinists, 1956; Publication (Box 246, Folder 8)
    Author: Fred Coonley
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: What does labor want?, a statement of trade union objectives by Al Hayes, 1950; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Primer for free Americans, 1951; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: This is aimed at you!, 1948; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: 'Right-to-work' laws; three moral studies, 1955; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: 50,000 foremen- who must listen, Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
    Notes: comic booklet/flyer. 2 copies
  - Item 6: Address by A.J. Hayes - Contract Negotiations - Adjustment of Grievances, 1950; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Statement presented Jan. 14, 1942 to the Executive Council - American Federation of Labor by H.W. Brown, Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: A.F. of L. Executive Council continues to shirk its responsibility; Time to call a halt; Where is our movement drifting?, 1942; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Steward's training course, 1953; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Strikers vs. Police, the rights and duties of each, Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Read what the International Association of Machinists did last year - 1913, Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Pension Plan, as amended Jan. 1, 1960, Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Committeeman pocket manual. Wage stabilization and job descriptions for office and technical employees, 1943; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Pocket manual Committeeman on Wage stabilization, job description, 1942; Publication (Box 247, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Read about a square deal, Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Union men backstop the nation, Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Penalty of neglect, Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Does your pay go for the Company's picnic?, Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: You need a great union, Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: To employees of the Metal Working Industry.. Some reasons why you should join, Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: This is to invite you to join the IAM..., Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Correspondence, 1948; Publication (Box 247, Folder 2)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The role of the AFL-CIO Ethical Practices Committee, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: One union for job security, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood dignity decency opportunity and justice..., Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Four good reasons why I joined the IAM, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Best automobile mechanics are IAM members, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Which car are you driving, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: What does labor want?, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: How the IAM protects its funds, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Labor Education Division, Roosevelt College, Film Programs, 1952; Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Machinists, Monthly Journal, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Making union meetings effective, 1950; Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
    Notes: manual prepared for Illinois State Conference of Machinists
  - Item 12: Testimonial tribute to Harvey W. Brown, retiring international president, International Association of Machinists., 1949; Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Boise, Idaho, and vicinity machinist apprenticeship standards, 1948; Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jointly adopted by representative employers and the International Association of Machinists, Local 1491, in cooperation with Bureau of Apprenticeship, U.S. Department of Labor
  - Item 14: Pocket guide for shop stewards., 1969; Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Los Trabajadores unidos en bien de la libertad, 1952; Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Pull as 1, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: From blue print, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: IAM standard of sound unionism, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: How the IAM elects its Officers, Publication (Box 247, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: promotional booklet telling about the IAM, 1956; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1953; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Your public relations, 1955; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
    Author: Gordon H. Cole
    Notes: article. 2 copies
  - Item 4: Correspondence, 1955; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: A new look at Health Insurance, 1955; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The meaning of the union shop in the labor movement, 1959; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: What to do about dermatitis, 1954; Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
    Author: William Alfred Sawyer
  - Item 8: Profile of International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 247, Folder 4)
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: You and your Governor Averell Harriman, A guide to victory in 1958, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Outline of 'Know your union' course, 1957; Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Machinist - Special Section & reprint from Dec. 12, 1957, 1957-1958 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Labor's stake in the public schools, 1957; Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: From blue print to blue sky!, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Making the Steward System work, 1957; Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: What's right with labor, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: How the IAM protects its funds, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: What does labor want?, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: How will you pay hospital, surgeon after you're 65?, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Labor's Uncertain trumpet, 1959; Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
    Author: H. W. Benson
    Notes: article reprinted from The Progressive, Madison, Wisconsin
  - Item 12: Things are rotten on 17th Streetand it's time for a change!!!, 1958; Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Here's how to run an honest union: be Honest, 1957; Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
    Author: Victor Riesel
  - Item 14: Toward a better, stronger America, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Know your union - the International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 247, Folder 5)
    Notes: article.
- International Association of Machinists (IAM), Publication (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Joint staff to aid on union benefits, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Pay-price dispute put up to Truman, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Republic pickets limited by court, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Excerpts from report by committee for White House Conference on Education, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Mediators set Parley on Republic walkout, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Pickets to be limited at Republic Monday, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Republic wins writ, bans mass picketing, 1948-1956 (Box 247, Folder 6)